Kenny Bowen-Than

SUMMARY

Hard-working team member with 3 years of work experience with a solid background in food service & customer service. Efficient and reliable worker with a strong ability to work under pressure. Aiming to leverage my abilities to successfully become a great employee at your company. Frequently praised as focused by my peers, I can be relied upon to help your company achieve it's goals.

OBJECTIVE

To obtain long term employment with growth potential with a company where I can contribute my hard working ability and my positive attitude.

EXPERIENCE

Cloud9 Pho & Tea Time - Bobarista & Waiter

Vancouver, Washington • 08/2021 - 08/2022

- Recommended products based on solid understanding of individual customer needs and preferences.
- Created wide variety of hot and cold drinks in average shifts with consistently positive customer satisfaction scores.
- Maintained supply levels in counter and customer areas to meet typical demands.
- Pleasantly interacted with customers during hectic periods to promote fun, positive environment.

Ocha Tea Corner - Bobarista

Portland. OR • 03/2021 - 07/2021

- Suggested food items to complement beverage orders.
- Cleaned prep areas and replenished supplies.
- Prepared beverage recipes and individually requested specialty drinks.
- Greeted guests with pleasant smile and superior customer service.

ShareTea Burnside - Bobarista

Portland, OR • 12/2019 - 10/2020

- Took customer orders and processed payment into the register
- Created bubble tea, toppings, and special order drinks with specialized equipment
- Kept the service line, kitchen, and guest lobby clean and tidy at all times.
- Managed orders and customer needs in a fast-paced environment
- Created personalized drinks if ever requested

CONTACT

kennybowent@gmail.com (503) 560-0969 Portland, OR 97266

SKILLS

- Efficient work under pressure
- Friendly customer service
- Cooperative team player
- Communication
- Dependable and reliable
- Food Serving and Preparation
- Customer Transactions
- Complaint Resolution

EDUCATION

High School Diploma Alliance High School Portland. OR • 06/2021